University Alumni Office - Record Group 32 WLU.RG.0032
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
University Alumni Office - Record Group 32
Date Not Yet Determined
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Washington and Lee University. Alumni Office
WLU.RG.0032
x Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
This record group contains materials created by Alumni Office during the course of its regular business, such as official publications and records about its management.
Online Access
View materials from this collection online via W&L's Digital Archive
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is generally open for research use. Some materials may be restricted.
- Richmond Virginia Chapter
  - Program of dinner in honor of the University's Board of Trustees, 1986; 1 Item
    Scope and Contents
    Program for a dinner held by the Richmond Virginia Chapter of the Washington and Lee University Alumni Association at the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts on October 24, 1986.
- Palm Beach-Fort Lauderdale Chapter
  - Louise Herreshoff: An American Artist Discovered and Reeves Collection of Chinese Export Porcelain exhibit preview invitation, 1979; 1 Item
    Invitation by Washington and Lee and the Palm Beach-Fort Lauderdale and Gulf Stream Alumni Chapters to a preview of the Reeves Center exhibits Louise Herreshoff: An American Artist Discovered and The Reeves Collection of Chinese Export Porcelain held at the Henry Morrison Flagler Museum on January 12, 1979.
    Art, American; Porcelain, Chinese; Washington and Lee University. Reeves Center; Herreshoff, Louise
- Texas Chapters
  - Invitations to annual Tex-Lex party, 1998-1999, 2003-2004; 4 Item
    Invitations to the annual Tex-Lex party for Washington and Lee University alumni from Texas. The events were held after the game on Parents Weekend.
- Alumni Association of China
  - The Washington and Lee University Alumni Association of China booklet, 1919-07; 1 Item
- New York Alumni Association
  - Proceedings upon the organization of the New York Alumni Association, Undated; 3 Item
- Louisiana Alumni Association
  - Banquet of Louisiana Alumni Association in honor of Hon. Luther Egbert Hall booklet, 1912-02-24
    Hall, Luther Egbert
- Alumni Association
  - Program for the annual meeting of the Washington and Lee Alumni Association, 2003, 2007, 2014; 3 Item
  - Welcome Class of... brochures, 1976-1978; 5 Item
  - Articles on Incorporation and By-laws, 1910-06-29
  - Board of Trustees booklet, 1969-06; 1 Item
  - Alumni fund, 1941-1972
    Contains Handbooks for Regional Agents, periodic bulletin sent to regional agents, various publications sent to alumni, and progress reports.
  - Charter, 1910-06-29; 1 Item
  - Recruitment Letter, 1916-12-06; 1 Item
  - Alumni-Admissions Program, 1984-1985; 1 Files
    General
    Includes Alumni-Admissions Handbook, 1984-1985 and October 1984 Newsletter.
  - Alumni Board. General Study Committee, 1983; Washington and Lee University. Alumni Board of Directors; Agelasto, Peter; Sessoms, Richard B.; Hurt, Charles D., Jr.; 1 Files
  - Alumni Board of Directors. Members, by-laws, etc., 1981-1984; Washington and Lee University. Alumni Board of Directors; Agelasto, Peter; Sessoms, Richard B.; Hurt, Charles D., Jr.; Huntley, Robert E. R. (Robert Edward Royall); 1 Files
    Includes the Washington and Lee University Alumni, Incorporated, Articles of Incorporation and By-Laws, Chartered, June 29, 1910.
    Washington and Lee University. Alumni Association; Huntley, Robert E. R. (Robert Edward Royall); Long, Charles Edward, Jr.; Washburn, William Crane
  - Alumni Board of Directors. Minutes, etc., 1979-1984; 2 Files
  - Alumni Board of Directors. Miscellaneous, 1979-1984; Washington and Lee University. Alumni Board of Directors; Agelasto, Peter; Hotchkiss, Farris Pierson; Sessoms, Richard B.; Washburn, William Crane; 2 Files
    Includes Leadership Conference Roster as of October 13, 1983.
  - Alumni Board. Planning comittee, 1982-1984; 1 Files
  - Alumni Board. Student Alumni Association, 1983-1984; 1 Files
  - The W&L Alumni College, Three Vacation Seminars booklet, 1 Files
  - Alumni House and Development of Chapters, 1981-1984; 1 Files
- Special Alumni Conference
  - Special Conference for Alumni Chapter Representatives program pamphlets, 1967-1972; 8 Item
  - Program Details and Reference Book, 1972-1979
  - Miscellaneous, 1967
    This file includes correspondence about the Special Alumni Conference, memos to faculty, an attendee roster, and event agendas.
- Class Reunions
  - 5th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
  - 10th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
  - 25th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
  - 35th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
  - 40th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
  - 45th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
  - 50th reunion of classes at Washington and Lee University
    - Programs. Celebration of Life. Washington and Lee University. Class of 1964 and 1965. 50th Reunion, 2014-05-02-2015-05-01
  - Class reunion event schedules
  - Class reunions honoring the Undergraduate and Law Classes
  - Five Star Generals Memorial Service and Celebration of Life, 2013, 2013-09-06
- Publications
  - Alumni Directory, 1749-2010
  - W&L: The Washington and Lee University Alumni Magazine, 1924-2013
    Online Access
    View issues since 2012 online
  - Opening Assembly, Alumni Weekend., 2014-05-01-2015-04-30
- Miscellaneous
  - Brochure on the Harmony House edition of "Washington and Lee University", 1986; Sessoms, Richard B.; 1 Item
    Brochure includes pictures from the book, information about the photograher William Strode, and a form for pre-ordering a copy. Includes a note from Richard B. Sessoms, Director of Alumni Programs
    Strode, William
  - List of alumni who were in the Confederate Service, Undated
  - Address to Washington and Lee Alumni: Convocation, 1954-06-12; 2 Item
    Speeches, addresses, etc., American
  - Memorial Service celebrating the life of Donald H. Peterson, 1931-1002, Class of 1953, Lee Chapel, Washington and Lee University., 2002-05-18
    Peterson, Donald H.